<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Possible neural analyses to compare CO and CST on CST Strategy Project Notes</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/</link><description>Recent content in Possible neural analyses to compare CO and CST on CST Strategy Project Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CO-CST covariance analysis</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211209-covariance-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211209-covariance-analysis/</guid><description>2021/12/09 CO-CST covariance analysis # For neural covariance analysis, we have a number of possible questions:
❓ Because CST has smaller movements, does neural variance also decrease as much as you would expect? 📊 Analysis: compare total neural variance between CO and CST ✔️ CST usually has smaller variance than CO, but unclear yet if it&amp;rsquo;s what we would expect from smaller movements ❓ Remiaining question: is this variance solely due to smaller movements?</description></item><item><title>CO Condition independent signal analysis</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211209-cis-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211209-cis-analysis/</guid><description>2021/12/09 Condition independent signal analysis # ❓ Is there a neural &amp;ldquo;go&amp;rdquo; signal underlying intermittent movements/control?
One result out of the literature recently has been that there are condition-independent signals (CIS) in neural activity that don&amp;rsquo;t relate to the exact movement being performed, but rather as a signal of whether a movement is being performed at all (see Kaufman et al. 2016, Rouse et al. 2018, Zimnik and Churchland 2021).</description></item><item><title>CST neural engagement</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211210-engagement-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211210-engagement-analysis/</guid><description>2021/12/10 Neural engagement analysis in CST # ❓ Is there a dimension of neural activity corresponding to neural engagement? Perhaps something that corresponds to whether $\lambda$ changed on the last trial, or whether there have been previous failures?
In Hennig et al. 2021, they found a neural dimension corresponding to engagement with the BCI task. When there were changes in the task (e.g. the decoder changes), activity along this axis increases and then slowly decreases over a series of trials.</description></item><item><title>CO-CST hold time analysis</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211210-hold-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211210-hold-analysis/</guid><description>2021/12/10 Hold time neural analysis # ❓ Are there dimensions of neural activity that separate CO and CST? ✔️ Hold time analysis says possibly in the very early part of the movement, but perhaps this is due to kinematic differences? Gallego et al. 2018 showed that M1 neural activity underlying multiple tasks shared some dimensions of neural activity, but also that there were certain dimensions of activity that separated different tasks.</description></item><item><title>CO-CST tangling analysis</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211214-tangling-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/neural-analyis-notes/20211214-tangling-analysis/</guid><description>2021/12/13 Tangling analysis # Overall task tangling # ❓ CST is much more feedback driven than CO. Does this show up as M1 dynamics being less apparently autonomous? That is, is neural tangling higher in CST than CO? ✔️ Tangling doesn&amp;rsquo;t really appear to be much higher in CST than CO, suggesting that the feedback may be &amp;ldquo;predictable&amp;rdquo; most of the time. 💬 Does tangling depend on the amount of data you use to check it?</description></item></channel></rss>