<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CO/CST comparison on CST Strategy Project Notes</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/tags/co/cst-comparison/</link><description>Recent content in CO/CST comparison on CST Strategy Project Notes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/tags/co/cst-comparison/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CO-CST hold time analysis</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/log/2021/12/hold-analysis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/log/2021/12/hold-analysis/</guid><description>❓ Are there dimensions of neural activity that separate CO and CST? ✔️ Hold time analysis says possibly in the very early part of the movement, but perhaps this is due to kinematic differences? Gallego et al. 2018 showed that M1 neural activity underlying multiple tasks shared some dimensions of neural activity, but also that there were certain dimensions of activity that separated different tasks. Though the tasks differed in the impedance of wrist movement (ranging from isometric to freely moving), the tasks were quite comparable: they were all wrist-based tasks with similar trial structure, where the monkey moved a cursor to visually presented targets within a set amount of time.</description></item><item><title>CO-CST covariance analysis</title><link>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/log/2021/12/covariance-analysis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raeedcho.github.io/cst-strat/log/2021/12/covariance-analysis/</guid><description>For neural covariance analysis, we have a number of possible questions:
❓ Because CST has smaller movements, does neural variance also decrease as much as you would expect? 📊 Analysis: compare total neural variance between CO and CST ✔️ CST usually has smaller variance than CO, but unclear yet if it&amp;rsquo;s what we would expect from smaller movements ❓ Remiaining question: is this variance solely due to smaller movements?</description></item></channel></rss>